<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>flonkerton</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on flonkerton</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PCI DSS</title>
      <link>/sensitive-data/pci/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sensitive-data/pci/</guid>
      <description>PCI DSS
Downloadable Files Raw Data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Identifiable Information</title>
      <link>/sensitive-data/pii/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sensitive-data/pii/</guid>
      <description>Personal identifiable information or PII is a class of sensitive data that includes peoples personal information such as name, ssn, address, etc. You can test a providers ability to block downloads of PII by attempting to download one of the files below. In order to test the ability to block uploads you can copy and paste the table below into the upload section of flonkerton, or upload a sensitive file to the same area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sensitive-data</title>
      <link>/sensitive-data/sesitive-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sensitive-data/sesitive-data/</guid>
      <description>Sensitive data is confidential or important information that an organization needs to protect. One of the primary reasons to use use flonkerton is to provide pseudo sensitive data that can be used for testing data protection solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upload Data</title>
      <link>/upload-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/upload-data/</guid>
      <description>Use this page to test data protection controls. Activities that can be tested here include form post, upload and even download(From the browse section).
Form Post Test This form will post data to the flonkerton api and write it to a file using the given name.
File name:
Data:
File Upload Test Select a single or multiple files to upload to flonkerton. If you controls are working these files will not appear below.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
